<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Coding With The Flow</title>
    <description>The personal encounters I have in my experiences as a programmer, and tinkerer.
</description>
    <link>http://derfoh.github.io/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://derfoh.github.io/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Fri, 19 Feb 2016 04:46:02 +0000</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 19 Feb 2016 04:46:02 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.1.1</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Changes to 841g site</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Lately I have been working on getting a website I made for a gaming comunity moved over to github pages. A lot of the sites that I have thrown together really only have basic needs in terms of the capability of what is required on the back end. As for web servers however after years of doing things such as trying to navigate a cPanel with millions of different functions spread haphazardly, to manually implementing a LAMP stack (or rather a LAP stack as I didn’t have much use for SQL until recently). I have found that at this point it is worth learning the way GitHub hosts their pages if your primary goal is to just make a basic site for a club or a group.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That being said we have changed much of the design at the site (you can check it out &lt;a href=&quot;http://841g.github.io&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In our case me (and another community manager) created an organization to keep things simpler when it came to both of us working on the site. It had become troublesome to get his fork up to date every time a pull needed to be made between the forks. We are both hoping that commiting to the same repo will simplify things.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m not sure though if for just us two this is more of a “nuclear option” and that it might be a bit overkill for just a small team. I wonder what aproaches other people generally take for this. For now though this works for us and hopefully if there are eventually more coding projects added under the org it will allow us to scale better as we get more members. I plan to eventually move a few of the bots that we use in our various group chats the group uses under the organization too in hopes that other members decide to work on them.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 17 Feb 2016 22:27:32 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>http://derfoh.github.io/check-in/2016/02/17/changes-to-841g-site.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://derfoh.github.io/check-in/2016/02/17/changes-to-841g-site.html</guid>
        
        <category>webdesign</category>
        
        <category>projects</category>
        
        
        <category>check-in</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Changing Default Git Shell</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Had some trouble finding an answer to this, maybe I was wording it wrong. Here it is in case there is another curious party.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To change the shell that you use do the following:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Click on the cog in the upper right of the GitHub gui&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Select &lt;code&gt;Options&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Directly under &lt;code&gt;Clone Path&lt;/code&gt; there is an option: &lt;code&gt;Default Shell&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Select the shell you want to use when you go to start&amp;gt;git shell&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Click Save&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now when you select Git Shell from your start menu it will open Git Bash.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 31 Dec 2015 15:02:27 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>http://derfoh.github.io/tips/2015/12/31/changing-default-git-shell.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://derfoh.github.io/tips/2015/12/31/changing-default-git-shell.html</guid>
        
        <category>tips</category>
        
        <category>git</category>
        
        <category>bash</category>
        
        
        <category>tips</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Undead Data</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;For my SQL class this semester we were asked to do a series of things that walked us through the creation of a great relational database. For my project our group decided on making a database for a fictional post-apocalyptic world where zombies are roaming the earth. Think watered down version of an application that could be used to keep track of the characters on popular television shows or movies. Another possible use for the design as discussed by my group is in making some sort of table top turn based game.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Wile the sole purpose of the project was just to create the database, not a front end, I decided to take things one step further for our deliverable for the end of the semester. I made it into a full LAMP stack website that demonstrated that the database and their queries can work with current web design standards.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Also this project allotted me a good excuse to learn a bit of PHP as I had minimal experience with it as a language prior to this experience. Ultimately while the code is clearly amateur it was a great way to learn a good variety of things such as but not limited to:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Basic PHP formatting and syntax&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Using PHP to connect to a SQL database&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Using PHP to query and draw the output into HTML tables.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;POST and GET operations&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Full LAMP Stack design philosophy&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Anyway here is a link to the project. I will probably keep it up indefinitely or until I decide I want to use that particular VPS for something different.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;undead-datahttpundeaddataderfohme&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://undeaddata.derfoh.me&quot;&gt;Undead Data&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Dec 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>http://derfoh.github.io/undeaddata/2015/12/18/undead-data.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://derfoh.github.io/undeaddata/2015/12/18/undead-data.html</guid>
        
        <category>projects</category>
        
        <category>Web Design</category>
        
        <category>LAMP</category>
        
        
        <category>UndeadData</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>VB Table Lookup</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;In my time  as a tutor I found that students struggled a lot with the concept of stepping through a multidemensional array. The concept of a table lookup is not necessarily the hardest thing to figure out but at the same time it takes a bit of thinking on the part of the programmer to conceptualize the logic behind it.
So the table looks somewhat like this:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;thead&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;th style=&quot;text-align: left&quot;&gt;Our Part&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th style=&quot;text-align: right&quot;&gt;Brand A&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th style=&quot;text-align: right&quot;&gt;Brand B&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th style=&quot;text-align: right&quot;&gt;Brand C&lt;/th&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/thead&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: left&quot;&gt;Our Part  1&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: right&quot;&gt;A1&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: right&quot;&gt;B1&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: right&quot;&gt;C1&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: left&quot;&gt;Our Part  2&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: right&quot;&gt;A2&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: right&quot;&gt;B2&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: right&quot;&gt;C2&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: left&quot;&gt;Our Part  3&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: right&quot;&gt;A3&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: right&quot;&gt;B3&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: right&quot;&gt;C3&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
  &lt;tfoot&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: left&quot;&gt; &lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: right&quot;&gt; &lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: right&quot;&gt; &lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: right&quot;&gt; &lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tfoot&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the case of this class the particular requirement of one of the applications the students make is that it has to go through an array of different parts made by different brands and it has to match that part up with the name of the part at the company. This lesson is a great way to introduce the capabilities of arrays as well as loops. I have also found that it is  a great way to introduce a student to Visual Studio’s debugger.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So the real meat is the code that steps through this array:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;language-vb&quot; data-lang=&quot;vb&quot;&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;k&quot;&gt;For&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;columninteger&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;ow&quot;&gt;As&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;kt&quot;&gt;Integer&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;=&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;mi&quot;&gt;0&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;k&quot;&gt;To&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;numberOfColumns&lt;/span&gt;    &lt;span class=&quot;c1&quot;&gt;&#39;steps through every row, this value can be changed to fit your needs.&lt;/span&gt;
	&lt;span class=&quot;k&quot;&gt;For&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;rowinteger&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;ow&quot;&gt;As&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;kt&quot;&gt;Integer&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;=&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;mi&quot;&gt;0&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;k&quot;&gt;To&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;numberOfRows&lt;/span&gt;   &lt;span class=&quot;c1&quot;&gt;&#39;steps through every column, this value can be changed to fit your needs.&lt;/span&gt;
		&lt;span class=&quot;k&quot;&gt;If&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;partsnumberstring&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;columninteger&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;,&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;rowinteger&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;)&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;=&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;PartsTextBox&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;Text&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;ToUpper&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;k&quot;&gt;Then&lt;/span&gt;
		&lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;MessageBox&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;Show&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s&quot;&gt;&quot;Found part: &quot;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;+&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;partsnumberstring&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;columninteger&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;,&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;rowinteger&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;)&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;+&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;s&quot;&gt;&quot;   --   Our Part: &quot;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;+&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;partsnumberstring&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;mi&quot;&gt;0&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;,&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;columninteger&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;))&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;c1&quot;&gt;&#39;if the string matches put out the value in the first column&lt;/span&gt;
		&lt;span class=&quot;k&quot;&gt;End&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;k&quot;&gt;If&lt;/span&gt;
	&lt;span class=&quot;k&quot;&gt;Next&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;k&quot;&gt;Next&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;what the code does is it steps through every column and row one by one cand compares the value in the text box that the user enters to the value found in that particular portion of the array. If the value matches the code outputs a message to the user that shows the part number they entered and the part number of the company’s part that matches it.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 17 Dec 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>http://derfoh.github.io/tips/2015/12/17/vb-table-lookup.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://derfoh.github.io/tips/2015/12/17/vb-table-lookup.html</guid>
        
        <category>tips</category>
        
        
        <category>tips</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>GadgetSearch</title>
        <description>&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;What is the application?
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;GadgetSearch is an application I made to teach my self as much android programming as I could. The primary reasoning behind this was that there are no applications that I could find that could search across on line retailers quickly for the latest and best technology.&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;What platform is it for?
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Currently Gadget Search is only for Android devices. There is no version of iOS devices planned for future releases.&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;What did you learn from making this?
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;I learned many of the basics of programming in Android. I primarily used the Eclipse editor in conjunction with the Android SDK to build and test the project. I have since ported my development work flow over to Android Studio.&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;The concepts of android that I got from this experience include:
        &lt;ul&gt;
          &lt;li&gt;Android Debugging&lt;/li&gt;
          &lt;li&gt;Basic Android Syntax and libraries&lt;/li&gt;
          &lt;li&gt;Design properties and layouts for front end UI&lt;/li&gt;
          &lt;li&gt;Calling another app and passing information between applications (in this case a key word)&lt;/li&gt;
          &lt;li&gt;How to use intents to start activities in other applications (in this case the bar code scanner)&lt;/li&gt;
          &lt;li&gt;Many other concepts associated with android development&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;/ul&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Where do I get it?
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Gadget Search can be downloaded from the &lt;a href=&quot;https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.derfohappco.gadgetsearch&quot;&gt;Google Play Store&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 16 Dec 2015 22:08:50 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>http://derfoh.github.io/gadgetsearch/2015/12/16/gadgetsearch.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://derfoh.github.io/gadgetsearch/2015/12/16/gadgetsearch.html</guid>
        
        <category>projects</category>
        
        
        <category>gadgetsearch</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Working with blog theme</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I had a heck of a time figuring out how to theme jekyll. You’d think there would be just one css file to edit but you would be very wrong. Apparently themes for Jekyll are an issue and are not very consistent in their implementation. Furthermore the things you might be seeing as local changes when building the site locally do not show up on github’s build of the site. I wasn’t aware that build errors get sent to your email so it was good that I learned that. Something as simple as changing the font color in the highlighted fields has proven to be very difficult however. It even took me a bit to figure out how to get the title of the blog to a different color. I persevered though in at least changing the color of the site’s title.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It seems that the file I need to edit in my directory is in the &lt;code&gt;_sass&lt;/code&gt; folder, the themes then seem to be laid out in a similar fashion to a regular css file but it looks like there are variables that can be set in the &lt;code&gt;css\main.scss&lt;/code&gt; file. This has been my first encounter with Sass files and find it intreguiing that you can use CSS in this way. There are a few more tweaks I’d like to do You can find more about this language at &lt;a href=&quot;http://sass-lang.com/&quot;&gt;http://sass-lang.com/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I also found a great resource for the type of markdown my Jekyll implementation is using (called kramdown) at &lt;a href=&quot;http://kramdown.gettalong.org/syntax.html&quot;&gt;http://kramdown.gettalong.org/syntax.html&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now that I have the site looking mostly how I want it to I am going to be working towards making more posts about the projects that I have currently on GitHub and go over their purpose, and if I expect to expand upon them.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 16 Dec 2015 19:43:53 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>http://derfoh.github.io/check-in/2015/12/16/working-with-blog-theme.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://derfoh.github.io/check-in/2015/12/16/working-with-blog-theme.html</guid>
        
        <category>theming</category>
        
        
        <category>check-in</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Archive page added!</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I found an easy way to implement an archive page into my Jekyll blog. Thanks to the author over at &lt;a href=&quot;http://reyhan.org&quot;&gt;reyhan.org&lt;/a&gt; I now have a simple archive page for the posts that I make to this log.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I had to add a file to my &lt;code&gt;_layouts&lt;/code&gt; directory called &lt;code&gt;archive.html&lt;/code&gt; that had the code from &lt;a href=&quot;http://reyhan.org/2013/03/jekyll-archive-without-plugins.html&quot;&gt;this site&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Then I added the archive.md so that the link would show up in the header. Next up I will be setting up analytics, and making it so that the front page is only limited to 5 posts.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 15 Dec 2015 17:24:50 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>http://derfoh.github.io/check-in/2015/12/15/archive-page-added.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://derfoh.github.io/check-in/2015/12/15/archive-page-added.html</guid>
        
        <category>theming</category>
        
        
        <category>check-in</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Remapping Caps to CTRL</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Found this helpful tip in a stack overflow after trying to get the caps lock key disabled on my keyboard.
Simply open powershell as an administrator and run the following commands then reboot. Your annoying caps lock key will be remapped to a much more useful control key.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;language-powershell&quot; data-lang=&quot;powershell&quot;&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nv&quot;&gt;$hexified&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;=&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;s2&quot;&gt;&quot;00,00,00,00,00,00,00,00,02,00,00,00,1d,00,3a,00,00,00,00,00&quot;&lt;/span&gt;.Split&lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s1&quot;&gt;&#39;,&#39;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;)&lt;/span&gt; | % &lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;{&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;s2&quot;&gt;&quot;0x&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nv&quot;&gt;$_&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s2&quot;&gt;&quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;}&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;nv&quot;&gt;$kbLayout&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;=&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;s1&quot;&gt;&#39;HKLM:\System\CurrentControlSet\Control\Keyboard Layout&#39;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;nb&quot;&gt;New-ItemProperty&lt;/span&gt; -Path &lt;span class=&quot;nv&quot;&gt;$kbLayout&lt;/span&gt; -Name &lt;span class=&quot;s2&quot;&gt;&quot;Scancode Map&quot;&lt;/span&gt; -PropertyType Binary -Value &lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;([&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;kt&quot;&gt;byte&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;[]]&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nv&quot;&gt;$hexified&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 15 Dec 2015 12:29:38 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>http://derfoh.github.io/tips/2015/12/15/remapping-caps-to-ctrl.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://derfoh.github.io/tips/2015/12/15/remapping-caps-to-ctrl.html</guid>
        
        <category>keymapping</category>
        
        <category>tips</category>
        
        
        <category>tips</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Getting Things Going</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I got most of the config worked out for this site. Jekyll has been an interesting experience getting set up. I also had to figure out how to set up the default config for a very useful sublime pluggin. Its worth checking out if you use Sublime text as your editor. It is called: &lt;a href=&quot;https://packagecontrol.io/packages/Jekyll&quot;&gt;sublime-Jekyll&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 15 Dec 2015 03:31:06 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>http://derfoh.github.io/check-in/2015/12/15/getting-things-going.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://derfoh.github.io/check-in/2015/12/15/getting-things-going.html</guid>
        
        <category>theming</category>
        
        
        <category>check-in</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Hello World!</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Hello! This is my first post to my code blog.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Setting up this blog with Jekyll was somewhat difficult overall it took me a few hours to figure out that I was missing half of the files I needed for this to work.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With a little help from a lot of googling though I finally think I have the basics down and at least now I can make posts. YAY!!!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Next up is getting this thing themed.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 15 Dec 2015 02:30:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>http://derfoh.github.io/check-in/2015/12/15/hello-world.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://derfoh.github.io/check-in/2015/12/15/hello-world.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>check-in</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
